<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="53">
    <author>yumi</author>
    <version>1.0.1.1</version>        
    <title>
        <en>Combine XPerience</en>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[
If you're tired of harvesting any crops with any combine at 10 kph, this mod is for you.
The goal of this mod is to provide a new experience when using combine harvesters in the game to be closer to real life harvesting. This is a first release and new features under development will arrive soon.
New features:
- Capability to activate combine and cutter independently as IRL
- Harvesting speed limit based on material quantity gathered, crop type and combine performance (based on power)
- Display several data in HUD when harvesting: material capacity (T/h), combine load (%), instant yield (T/ha)
==== CHANGELOG ====
Fixed in v1.0.0.1
- Capability to reach combine load up to 120% to be able to keep 100% more easily with high yield crop
- Higher speed for MF Activa 7347 and forage harvesters
- No more error when mod zip file is renamed
- Warning message translation
Fixed in v1.0.0.2
- HUD text scaling issue
- HUD error when playing on Dedicated Server
- Better management of sugarbeet and potatoes harvesters
New in v1.0.1.0
- Adding russian translation
- Engine revs up when threshing and overloading
- Engine load and speed depending on crop moisture if Seasons mod enabled or on time of the day
Fixed in v1.0.1.1
- Higher speed for forage harvesters cutters like mex5
]]></en>
        <fr><![CDATA[
Si vous en avez assez de moissonner n'importe quelle culture avec n'importe quelle moissonneuse à 10 km/h, ce mod est pour vous.
Le but de ce mod est de fournir une nouvelle expérience lors de l'utilisation des moissonneuses-batteuses dans le jeu pour être plus proche de la réalité. Il s'agit d'une première version et de nouvelles fonctionnalités en cours de développement arriveront bientôt.
Nouvelles fonctionnalités:
- Possibilité d'activer la moissonneuse-batteuse et la barre de coupe indépendamment comme IRL
- Limite la vitesse de moisson en fonction de la quantité récoltée, du type de culture et des performances de la moissonneuse (basées sur sa puissance)
- Affiche différentes données dans le HUD lors de la récolte: quantité de récolte (T/h), charge de la moissonneuse (%), rendement instantané (T/ha)
==== CHANGELOG ====
Fixed in v1.0.0.1
- Possibilité d'atteindre une charge machine de 120% pour être en mesure de conserver 100% plus facilement lors d'une récolte à haut rendement
- Vitesse plus élevée pour MF Activa 7347 et les ensileuses
- Plus d'erreur lorsque le fichier zip mod est renommé
- Traduction des messages d'avertissement
Fixed in v1.0.0.2
- Problème de mise à l'échelle du HUD
- Erreur du HUD lors d'une partie sur Dedicated Server
- Meilleure gestion des récolteuses de betteraves et de pommes de terre
New in v1.0.1.0
- Ajout de la traduction russe
- Le moteur monte en régime lors du battage et du déchargement
- Charge machine et vitesse dépendante de l'humidité de la culture si le mod Seasons est actif ou de l'heure de la journée sinon
Fixed in v1.0.1.1
- Vitesse plus élevée pour les ensileuses trainées telles que la mex5
]]></fr>
        <de><![CDATA[
Wenn Sie es satt haben das Feld mit einem beliebigen Mähdrescher bei 10 km/h zu ernten, ist dieser Mod genau das richtige für Sie.
Das Ziel dieses Mods ist es, eine neue Erfahrung bei der Verwendung von Mähdreschern im Spiel zu bieten, um denen im Reallife näher zu kommen. Dies ist eine erste Version und neue Funktionen, die derzeit entwickelt werden, werden in Kürze verfügbar sein.
Eigenschaften:
- Mähdrescher und das Schneidwerk unabhängig voneinander als IRL zu aktivieren
- Erntegeschwindigkeitslimit basierend auf der gesammelten Materialmenge, der Ernteart und der Mähdrescherleistung (basierend auf der Power)
- Zeigt Ihnen bei der Ernte mehrere Daten im HUD an: Materialkapazität (T/h), kombinierte Ladung (%), sofortiger Ertrag (T/ha)
==== CHANGELOG ====
Fixed in v1.0.0.1
- Möglichkeit, eine Maschinenlast von bis zu 120% zu erreichen, um während einer Ernte mit hohem Ertrag 100% leichter zu halten
- Höhere Geschwindigkeit für MF Activa 7347 und Feldhäcksler
- Kein Fehler mehr beim Umbenennen der Mod-Zip-Datei
- Übersetzung von Warnmeldungen
Fixed in v1.0.0.2
- Problem mit der HUD-Textskalierung
- HUD-Fehler beim Spielen auf einem dedizierten Server
- Besseres Management von Zuckerrüben- und Kartoffelerntern
New in v1.0.1.0
- Russische Übersetzung hinzufügen
- Motor beschleunigt beim Dreschen und Überladen
- Motorlast und Drehzahl hängen von der Feuchtigkeit der Ernte ab, wenn der Seasons Mod aktiviert ist oder von der Tageszeit
Fixed in v1.0.1.1
- Higher speed for forage harvesters cutters like mex5
]]></de>
        <ru><![CDATA[
Если вам надоело убирать поле любым комбайном на скорости 10 км/ч, этот мод для вас.
Цель этого мода - дать новый опыт использования комбайнов в игре, чтобы приблизиться к реальному. Это первая версия, и вскоре будут доступны новые функции, которые разрабатываются в настоящее время.
Свойства:
- Активировать комбайн и жатку независимо друг от друга как "в реальной жизни"(IRL)
- Ограничение скорости сбора урожая в зависимости от количества собранного урожая, типа урожая и производительности комбайна (в зависимости от его мощности)
- Отображает несколько данных в HUD во время уборки: производительность комбайна (т/ч), загрузка комбайна (%), текущая урожайность (т/га)
==== ИЗМЕНЕНИЯ ====
Fixed in 1.0.0.1
- Возможность достижения нагрузки комбайна до 120%, чтобы было легче удерживать 100% при высокой урожайности
- Более высокая скорость для MF Activa 7347 и кормоуборочных комбайнов
- Больше нет ошибок при переименовании zip-файла мода
- Перевод предупреждающего сообщения
Fixed in 1.0.0.2
- Проблема с масштабированием текста HUD
- Ошибка HUD при игре на выделенном сервере
- Лучшее управление свёкло- и картофелеуборочными комбайнами
New in 1.0.1.0
- Добавление русского перевода
- Двигатель набирает обороты при обмолоте и разгрузке
- Нагрузка на двигатель и скорость в зависимости от влажности урожая, если включен мод Seasons, или от времени суток
Fixed in v1.0.1.1
- Higher speed for forage harvesters cutters like mex5
]]></ru>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>modIcon.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="src/main.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>

    <l10n>
        <text name="warning_firstStartThreshing">
            <fr>Vous devez d'abord démarrer le système de battage</fr>
            <en>You first need to start combine threshing</en>
            <de>Starten Sie zuerst das Mähdrescher-Dreschsystem!</de>
            <ru>Сначала запустите систему обмолота комбайна!</ru>
        </text>
    </l10n>

</modDesc>
